uh you know like when
um
just anybody says don't take things
personally
just you hear that they don't take it
personally part of you kind of understands to a
part of you kind of understands to a
degree
what that means
you will not be like what what does that
even mean you would have some internal
reference point for
for not taking things personally
so how would you so how do you not take
things personally again no need to call
the sisters or something like that just
what is the internal internal attitude
when you hear
hey don't take things personally and
then you're just yeah okay I should try
and not take things personally what
would you try what would you do how
would you pay more objective and
um your
analysis of the situation so that that
can come as a result of not taking
things personally but really we're
talking about the internal attitude we
will have towards yourself
so what described that attitude how
would you not take yourself personally
because as I said sure you will not be
able to do it in that
thorough manner that the suitors would
describe because that requires a little
bit more
but people can and they understand to a
people can and they understand to a
degree and can actually exercise the
attitude of not taking things personal even if
of not taking things personal even if
their behavior is not purified and
developed and everything else they could
still not don't take it personally and keep
not don't take it personally and keep
the Mind above personal involvement is
is definitely a sense of
okay don't take it personally okay
you you meet the intern you've tried to
relax and calm yourself yeah step back
yeah okay okay
because like we spoke about it before
the choice it becomes apparent
you know like whether how much you'll be
involved with your thoughts greed
aversion delusion well this is also a
choice it's apparent again obviously the how
it's apparent again obviously the how
how efficient you're choosing will be
that depends on other factors we can
talk about it but initially you can
choose to not take things personal to a
degree and you can do it to them to to
that other matching that level so to
speak so I'm trying to find out what
that attitude is
how would you describe it so it's just
something that you can actually practice
so what how do you take yourself
in the attitude of not taking yourself
personal what's your attitude towards
yourself not myself
so thinking yourself as not yourself not
as mine not as yours so the entirety of
your sense of self or your experience as
a whole you turn against and say
I won't take this as mine
and that does remain an option
as I said how how deep that option will
reach that depends on other factors but
to some extent even like as I said
completely undeveloped person with you
know basic faculties and intelligence
can stop and think about it and say yeah
okay I'll go throughout my day not
taking things personally
um
what else how else what are the
characteristics of that would you would
you single out
to not take the significance of
whatever things
for granted like the implications of
whatever happens
that's like
as it presents in a way the way I would
use it sure so okay so have basically
keep the perspective in regard to things
that you're experiencing because again
the perspective is that that which makes
you not take things personally
would you say it
it should have not taken yourself
personally could be exemplified through
could be exemplified through
seeing yourself in a third person sense
if you were to kind of remember this
whole what somebody told you don't take
things personally then you can take that
you can turn the same attitude towards
to it anything you think anything you
feel anything you intend Here and Now
and not take it personally because it is
always on the level of this most
immediate Choice slash attitude
whether you're going to be personally
involved or whether you're going to keep
that context and perspective of I shall
not be personally involved with this
situation so
what happens if you what is the most
General characteristic if you when you
are personally involved with the
situation ignoring ignoring loss of context
ignoring ignoring loss of context
absorbed you are absorbed in the objects
of your experience the attitude of being
just absorbed into day-to-day things in
your senses in your thoughts and not
having perspective on yourself in the
situation that's already a symptom of
having taken things personally so
you could be thinking about how not to
take things personally when somebody
says this somebody does that but if you
are absorbed in that
with same lack of awareness you are
taking that personally of course yes and
that's the point here you recognize that
all these emotions all these things you
might do out on that kind of their
secondary to that basic choice of before
I act by Body by speech or by mind
the most fundamental Choice the most
fundamental direction that I have is go
with it I take it personally
refrain from it maintain perspective
which will prevent me from taking
personally as much
and do do people see now what else is
mirrored through this
okay that's that's too easy
no no I mean this this is like going
with it or not going with it oh this has
to do with this exactly yeah and that's
how you would start the sense restraint
and keeping the precepts in virtue
because unknowingly you're already
diminishing the degree of taking things
personal even if you don't actually know
anything about personality or not taking
things personally never heard an art and
so on
that and that's that's that was the
point it was this was leading to that's
why people can understand the attitude of
people can understand the attitude of
not taking things personally and they
can do it to a degree but if their
behavior is not developed if the choices
and actions are not purified it it's
gonna work for a few few moments for as
much as you have developed your
composure which means very little
and then it will become abstract it will
become that secondary psychologization
of United personally while everything is
taken personally here and now
um and that's because the actions rooted
in greed
last sensuality desire aversion ill will
annoyance distraction
delusion indolence ignorance all of
those attitudes are attitudes that uh
the fuel personality and they maintain
it yeah so even if you are saying to
yourself in the meantime and try to
genuinely like honestly practice the
attitude of not taking things personally
if you're still acting
out of those reasons that is your
personality and that's why the mind will not listen
and that's why the mind will not listen
so to speak
but if you were to purify your behavior
that which you already know
to a degree
as I said like colloquially oh don't
take it personally I find that very
useful you should try it and you would
have some internal relationship with
that thought so to speak they would
resemble some attitude that you can do
and develop
but as I said it's uh it's too subtle
and it's it's uh too easy to just fall
off back onto the secondary circularization
back onto the secondary circularization
and ideas because the mind is not
developed and the mind is not developed because
and the mind is not developed because
the behavior is not developed and
purified so can we find Arguments for
this like is there an argument that
shows that lack of sense restraints
increases the possibility of taking
things personally or is it just so much
of Faith just start doing that and then
discern for themselves yeah uh you can
you can find a you can find as I said if
you start describing that you should
have taken things personally as we did
first thing it was oh you kind of have
perspective so whatever comes your way
you don't just go for it because you
realize right there and then
you don't know if it's good or bad
doesn't matter you're just talking about
if you go for it go to bed you will not
be able to keep perspective on of
yourself in this situation you will lose
the sight of yourself because you went
for the things that were presented
exactly so side sounds melt these
touches feelings and so on yeah and you
okay so if your goal is to keep the
perspective you realize anything they
would absorb you away from it is is
contradicted he's canceling it yeah and
then expand that same principle and see
okay so what are the things that the
foremost of things that make you
absorbed in them and take you away from
here and now basically where you are
self-aware well sensualities the
foremost ill will is the foremost
distraction delusion indolence yeah so
you don't need Faith to recognize that
you will see now you might need Faith to
stick to not taking things personally
um or some seriously penetrative wisdom
developed in a kind of your own
intellect but uh one way or the other it
needs to be done
you can choose to not take things
personally and develop a view and so on
but are you now upholding what you chose
are you now upholding what you chose
through your behavior are you preventing
yourself from eroding the principle of
not taking things personally that you
yourself want to develop and see a
degree of benefit in it or are you
actually you know like making the effort
and restraining and then it will become
even a parent that you don't even need
to maintain that attitude well I won't
take this person I must I must not
forget not to take things personally
because you're not taking it personally
by Body speech and mind and those are
the three ways you take things
personally try it and you will have a
degree of release you would have a
degree of space safety created
internally simply by not having not
taken that thing personally
and if you stick to that and say
what if I clarify this
this little relief and see how far it
can go
what if I really push it all the way
and and and make it my being and see
because so far it only results in
release yeah of of this pleasure
yeah of of this pleasure
which you are very well versed with by
being alive by experiencing feeling
pulls pressures
and so on
like like that's also why
like that's also why
um
you know this uh either being absorbed
with things or having perspective in
regard to things
the it's it's very much it follows the
same um structure of the gradual training in
um structure of the gradual training in
terms of what needs to be done when so
to speak as in you start by taking the
precepts and keeping the virtue but then
the next like when it describes you know
sends restraint and guarding the sun
stores which is kind of what would come
um on top of that
is like could basically need to be some
summarized by saying don't be absorbed
in what your eyes see what you're when
seeing a size with the eyes when hearing
sometimes with the ear
don't um kind of grasp feeling Sensations
um kind of grasp feeling Sensations
significance of whatever object yeah or
whatever whatever and that's that's for
those other General descriptions say
exactly it doesn't grasp any signs and
features that's yeah
so that's kind of
just taking the exact same principle
even further yeah well there was also I
think well I don't know the specificity I
well I don't know the specificity I
think a number of them but it would have
been it would start with a description
of a gradual training uh keep a virtue
keeping the precepts guarding of the
sandstorm being moderated eating and
then he goes to an empty Hut or a root
of a tree and contemplates as as this
Hut as this room is empty of others so
is this experience empty of personality
and to yourself and you realize why you
don't start with those thoughts I mean
you can but they will be abstract
but if you have actually tamed the the
wild animal of your mind desires and so
on through guarding the sense those
diligent uh sensory strength then these
thoughts cease to be abstract they
become very applicable
or I am no one to anything anywhere at
21 anywhere in the world and nobody
anywhere in the world is anything to me
so it's like there is no personality
here or in others not in between the two
not in any direction
um but that's not just like a view that
somebody would be chanting or singing
along or something as their belief it
becomes an actual applicable attitude if
applied after or on top of the properly
after or on top of the properly
developed gradual training but my point
here is that you don't need more
instruction you already have a threat
you already have a threat
of recognition what not taking things
personally is
and if that's too abstract or if that's
not resulting in Greater releases or
it's because your behavior still hasn't
been purified sufficiently
you haven't taken responsibility for
intentions and actions and that needs to
be tamed and endured and then this this
will just start into place because it's
always there because you already know it
but I think the really
um
the thing that most people do not have
when they or do not think when they hear
don't take things personally is what you
said don't take the feeling personally
yeah for example
yeah no taking things if you if you have
not taken it personally you will not be
able to act out of it so the fact are
you acting out of your feelings
then by thought by speech by mind means
well you are taking it personal they're
moving you so you don't have perspective
so yeah so it's not just like oh
it was oh relax don't take things
personally but it's all I will not take
anything personally did I become aware
of
feeling form Sensations perceptions
anything I shall not take personality I
should remain the third person point I
should remain contemplating and keeping
it upholding the third person point of
view so to speak as the Buddha called it
um in another Suitor
all things the entire experience
whatever comes and goes past future
traumas happiness doesn't matter all of
that converges on the feeling Here and
Now not in the past not in the future
and that's why the Liberation is also
like here and now in that same sense
first you need to accept the fact that
yeah so you are subjected to feelings to
pressures to sensuality to your will
like see you don't want people know
anger is bad and so on but when it's
there it's like and then afterwards
you're remorseful and so on
so you have to recognize that okay so
you are liable and you don't know how to
remain unmoved by those things
so as as we already said the successful
practice of not taking things personally
cannot be done unless Behavior has been
developed beforehand and by that I mean
unless you have sufficiently not acted
out of central desire ill will
irritation ignorance boredom indolence
distraction everything else that's
unwholesome and all of those are choices
that you make at a time and if you act
towards them it's because you chose to
ignore how not to take things personally
would it be someone correct than to say
that um
um
this is why I've always I've to be
honest I've always found this kind of a
I used to find it not really a useful
advice don't take it personally because
I'd be just thinking I can't help it I
can't help it here personally it's not a
choice that I can make which is true but
you can kind of recognize that there are
choices you can make that will yeah like
immediately result in taking things
personally much less and then for
further choices that will then become
sort of available
but even even within like say the the
overall picture yeah you can't just not
take things personally but part of you
understands the degree of possibility
that would be if I wouldn't take things
personally no I'll just I don't want to
think about it I'll carry on doing what
I'm doing but if you stop and think
about it my point was that even
colloquially untrained mind would have a
threat of recognition for what it is in
the same sense if somebody says oh just
relax yeah like relax like relax your
body like you don't need you don't need to be
like you don't need you don't need to be
educated for that you don't need to
learn any special techniques or methods
or yoga nothing you would know
internally to a degree
you will have the attitude of relaxation
of certain letting go to a degree
now the fact that you can't sustain that
longer is because everything else that
you do and choose and responsibility
that you avoid and so on you completely
constantly disturbing it so then you can
keep saying relax relax but five minutes
before that you were acting on a desired
and shouting so it's already out of
anger so that's like well
saying one thing doing Heather exactly
saying one thing doing the other
thinking one thing and then saying the
other and doing the other
so but if you actually stop and think
about it you realize there is already a
recognition of that
just how to relax and there is already
the recognition of how to not take it
personally because you could when the
mind is balanced say you're not affected
right there and then with ill will with
anger with sensuality with distraction
with sleepiness you're sort of just
balanced and that experience if you start
and that experience if you start
thinking about it can I not take this
personally you would have some sense you
would you would have a degree of
understanding there
and then see why cannot I extend this
attitude throughout my day regardless of
what feelings come up
but how others act around me can I
remain impersonal
impersonal
point of view
and there was that other suit that says
the foremost of The Outsiders views
falls down to exactly like basically
there is no person either here but seen
in that Here and Now present manner not
not on the level of some sort of
explanation they would then say well
nothing matters because and then this is
how most people would take like a
Buddhism in a traditional sense
everything is constantly changing
nothing is really ours but that is very
much yours because if somebody upsets
you you would feel it if somebody
provokes you you would feel it if
somebody distracts you you would act out
of it so if you have thought of me
personally you're just having this
pasting kind of on top of a wound that's
you know putting a sticker that says not
person but it's very much in fact a
person
so that's why NATA can be understood
only on the basis of fully understanding
on each
the result of it
but yes discomfort
changeability unknown ability
impermanence how you want to translate
it you recognize those things here and
now doesn't matter the conditions doesn't
doesn't matter the conditions doesn't
matter other people
see the fact that if you are not
ignoring the fact that things are
subject to change even while they're
permanent permanently enduring here
there is a possibility of the change at
any given time
that's already going to prevent you from
taking it personally
to the extent you would otherwise
so forgetting about Anita is another
symptom of having being absorbed
absorbed and takenings personally
forgetting the things because they're
subject to change at any given time thus
they are this uncomfortable
to that extent they are unpleasant
forgetting that discomfort
is again going to make you take things
personal not forgetting the implicit
discomfort of change
you already have a better perspective
yeah Sonata is the result of the right
practice of right understanding of an
agenduka
I'm keeping that context alive not
forgetting it the result of it is you
are not touching anymore you let it go yeah
not touching anymore you let it go yeah
how would you keep the context alive
what's the what's the uh this the
suitable fuel
for keeping that context burning
aside from Central streaming Thursday
more immediately what would be the
what's the immediate fuel for
for
taking things personal or not
whatever you're currently feeling
so it's doesn't matter the mass of
confusion you might
feel or think about an account with this
or that
the point of convergence is how it is
being felt in its broadest terms don't
take that personally and you have
created a space between you and the
entire pressure so how do you keep the
context of the nature yeah yeah so you
can to to basically constantly recollect
and not lose sight of what you're
currently feeling what feeling is kind
of enduring I was thinking because
that's another suit you remember
uh
the how do you know you've taken things
how do you know you've taken things
personally it's because you're pressured
you are contacted the unpressured you
are affected
so that's you can know oh yeah and how
does it that you feel that yeah you feel
that you know so
the convergence Point feeding yeah if
you feel
to a degree that there is a feeling to
that degree there is some conceitful
sense of I am that's why other hand is
the one for whom there is nothing felt
as the suit is described what is it
because there are no traces of
Personality left pressures pressure one
who is attached to
wonder who's holding how could precious
pressure one who's
the ground this one yeah yeah
but there is no basis for anything to be
pressured yeah
yeah and so that seriously like you
don't start as an arrow hunt as I said
so you're going to have some degree of
pressure some degree of feeling
but through keeping perspective in
regard to what you're feeling
that was already well make your sense
restraint easier
certainly be
freeing you from remorse or wrongdoing
and also by remaining aware of what
current feeling is enduring here and now
to that extent you are not observed in
it and that is the that is the way of
not taking personally so you might think
like oh I shall I shall keep this
context of not taking things personally
Alive by constantly reminding and
thinking about it in any suits and stuff
but they will kind of wave it away you
know inspiration comes and goes that's
just how these things work
but if you find things like
pressures um feeling
um feeling
even your your current body posture
State nature of it what is subjected to
all those things are on the level of
here and now and all of those things
can't stand as that convergence point
from which you can remain
impersonal towards it to a degree at
least and then cultivate that further by
not making it worse through unwholesome
and unskillful actions or you can ignore
it and then get absorbed in this in
those sense objects
and that's exactly why a noble disciple
in the suit does the one who is
committed to the gradual training they
would encourages them to constantly
remind and contemplate not mine not for
me not I am
in regard to everything that comes their
way
and as we said already that will have a
practical result
result
because they are developed in body
speech and mind they're committed to the
to The Taming of the Mind
the question regarding sense restraint
especially for those on the you know
gradual path where you know often
especially at the beginning
um
well I guess I see a tendency for toward
rigidity and toward
and toward
taking sense restraint personally
um especially I see
um a lot of young men uh with maybe
aggressive mentalities coming to the
monastery and they want to do the new
tangas and they want to
um you know all of these things and and
it doesn't it's not sustainable for them
they leave yeah
um
how can one have an attitude that
doesn't that that's sustainable that
that doesn't lead there and that's not
based in rigidity and uh taking
personally of I am
someone who's restrained
well first and foremost is to learn what
actual sensation is because the tangas
are not sense restrained
a piece of the sense restraint so you
don't need to be not laying down and
eating out of your bowl and wearing rag
ropes but you need to not tolerate thought
but you need to not tolerate thought
sensuality even when you're sitting in a
comfortable chair
even if you're even for a layperson who
is not
um who is not capable to take on these
dotangas and find such an environment
you realize well has nothing to do with
the practice
none of those aesthetic practices have
anything to do with the practice if they
do
in a positive manner it's for those who
already understood what a practice is
and then they would see a direct
relationship between those Batangas and
Improvement in their practice
so all those young men need to learn
basically what the dhamma is
that's it they come there they inspired
they try to just like overpower
everything but it's like but that's
that's like you you know you get a
guitar that's too loose
somebody tells you you need to tighten
the strings and you smash the guitar
that's the attitude
so initially there will be some rigidity
even when it comes to just uh sense
restraint for somebody who is very
unrestrained but again by learning what the precepts
but again by learning what the precepts
are where the line is
you can then relax within that without
becoming too loose
because initially see if you take
rigidity to be a problem in and of
itself any form of saying no to yourself
is a form of rigidity to that extent
it's like well no I must have been rigid
correct but I must not go back to
sensuality either that's also correct
so until that balance is found there's
going to be some rigidity involved even
with basic sense restraint and file
preset trade presets not even going into
the tangles
is there a role for
joyful practice in
um leading to that kind of restraint and
and I guess I'm asking like as an
alternative to willpower how can we
cultivate a mind that tends toward
restraint through a sense of restraint okay yeah
through a sense of restraint okay yeah
that's like as the surtas will describe
often only after you've been withdrawn
and learn and understood the benefit of
it then the mind will naturally incline
towards occlusion on sensuality
there is no
um sort of a sweet peel you can take in
the beginning before that understanding
but that understanding can only come
through actually doing it first
and that's why the similes in the sutas
were always about you know trapping a
wild elephant
and then
knocking the stakes in the ground
leather straps and then it's it's it's
urinating defecating screaming fighting
against it and then you just have to
wait until it comes down
and it comes down then you offer a bit
of food it refuses okay you wait no
they're not okay it takes the food
starts to recognize you starts to listen
that's the mind yeah
so
if you still kind of
have a desire for finding a way of
Joyful practice
probably a useful thing to would be to
understand why why would that be
important why would joyful practice be important
why would joyful practice be important
at this stage
like say somebody gives you a medicine
that's really bitter and makes your
whole body ridges for a while
but you factually know and you can
reason yourself that it is a beneficial
medicine so then but you I won't take it unless I
so then but you I won't take it unless I
can take it with sugar but you can't
because sugar cancels the effects of the
medicine what's the problem what's the problem
what's the problem what's the problem
with this
why is this so unacceptable to me that I
need to make you joyful
because if I'm actually paying my mind
then everything will be joyful
effortlessly I will need to make it it
will be the result of successful
withdrawal I mean Janna the whole the
whole practice of it is exactly that you
finally feel thoroughly in like the the
deepest parts of your being you feel
free from debt from Peril from threat
from anything that can harm you and
that's the result of withdrawal from the
five hindrances they were the result of
withdrawal from unwholesome states by
bodies picture mind
so yeah joyfulness and joy
it should be cultivated but
kind of in its own time when it comes as
a result of the draw off
not before
and it sort of mirrors similar
same vijana you should call it vagina
and you should cultivate that the
pleasure that comes is so people want to
start a practice with that
I want the pleasure of Janna
to overwhelm me make me feel great and
then all the hard work of restraining
sense desires will fall away because I
got the genre but then actually I tend
to suit this closely it's always no
that's the result of undoing all of this
so yeah
and there was a generosity you know one
of the first things is yeah being
generous because actually as you said
being virtuous in the basic sense being
generous that's already it will make it
easy but well you will be less hard to
yeah and you can be recollecting those
things there's no there is no harm in
doing that even food like to uplifting
of you know moves factually like when
when the disciple you collects his
unbroken virtue
his generosity
it's like oh yeah the mind the mind will
be more joyful on account of that
um but as long as
Joy is an experience on account of those
right Reflections it's fine not with its
experience on account of compromising
the initially rigid state of precepts or
sense restraint
then that's not the wholesome Joy
yeah that's say that
something
basically what you were saying in about
that you need to say no to yourself to
some things but not to everything that's
like one sentence you think oh yeah yeah
that sounds makes sense but in practice
it's really something that
it takes quite a bit of work to
understand what you need to say no to
and look you need to kind of realize
that it is something that needs to be
understood and you just don't just kind
of take for granted the things to to say
no to apart from the precepts like the
precepts of you know the basic things
but then on top of that whatever is
rooted in
in greed in aversion delusion in on
wholesome intentions is kind of a
it's not something that you already
start you start with some understanding
of that but then you still need to
develop understanding of what that means
and kind of yeah
how deep it goes how far it goes to what
extent you know on the level of thoughts
of speech or whatever like small things
that would seem fine but you
um but then and then also not allow
yourself to Verge into
like yeah like very easy then to kind of
Virgin to just kind of saying no to
anything Pleasant for example or not
using whatever happens to be agreeable
because I don't know whatever
that's that's quite a yeah but basically to
that's quite a yeah but basically to
find that line is to develop the Right
View so it kind of to realize that okay
it's normal that it shouldn't be clear
in the beginning that I have to work to
understand it because if I fully develop
understanding of you in this basic
principle that's that's developing the
Right View like essentially becoming a
sort of balance so it's yeah just to
kind of realize that it's not a trivial
thing will already make you do it better
yeah measure the task rightly what needs
to be done recognizing Center that's
closer to success
yeah that is the the suit is also
described that satapana is the one who
understands uh wholesome is wholesome
good as good and bad is bad
which means nobody who is not a solar
panel does not fully understand the
depth of what makes good good and bad
bad everybody can have an idea about it but
everybody can have an idea about it but
fully understanding that principle
seeing it for yourself what is
beneficial what is unbeneficial that's
the third party yeah [Music]
because yeah because you all said it
because like it can be like okay yeah so
the presets the the sense of chain I do
good I don't do bad and then I do the
practice I was like no that is the
practice doing that and then fully
understanding the principle of that that
is the practice that is not exactly
knowing what's what leads to
Enlightenment and what doesn't yeah
exactly and but people people by not
seeing that is how they would then go
and jump into these nutangas or super
inspirational agents and so on is that
not recognizing that that's the degree
they have to stay on
they just want okay so if I keep doing
this and Titan Titan Titan Titan Titan
Deadpool is up and one way or the other
whether people commit to meditation
techniques that result in being fully
absorbed in Your Body Sensations or
whatever else or commit to to Tanga and
random observances they do it for that
same reason impatient wanting to avoid
things being endured on the right level
that's a pride
yeah yeah that goes and yeah concede
Center I am none of that because that is
actually being dissolved if you stay on
the level of the feeling where
everything else converges and by that I
also mean you don't act out of it to
prolong it but you don't like that way
to get rid of it because it's not yours
to begin with
why why jumping into the tongue or
something what's the problem with this
are you engaging sincerity no you will
no that's business remorse no okay well
then stop stop there but it becomes
uncomfortable to stay there because your
death you're if you are staying at that level
you're if you are staying at that level
you cannot take things personally and
from a personality point of view that
feels unpleasant that feels threatening
so now you're staying with another layer
of threat that's dissolving your
personal point of view and that's kind
of the sort of bug
which is why when people who did not
quite want or were not quite ready to
understand the Buddhist teaching but
they insisted that he explained it to
them when he did they sort of went into
complete panic mode saying the suit is
described they would fall on the ground
pull their hair and be their breasts in
kind of in despair saying oh that would
well that will kill me that will destroy
me that will cancel and completely
annihilate who I am he's like yeah
that's exactly what it will do
but they don't see The Liberation and
joy of that they just see a threat
because that is for for many with that
that will be the first kind of thing
that arises so that's why then people
will just not want to stay on that level
which is not that hard to kind of
discern but hard to keep yourself at
because you would then either wanna all
just do these practices or uphold these
little things or do these techniques or
methods so I don't have to stay on this
level where I am self-aware
and when that kind of uncertainty of the
choices the weight of the actions
convergence points it's all felt
pressuring here
no just tell me what to do I said I
think about it I mean how many times we
heard that oh yeah